[Music]
Most people look at risk as one pulled
element. But when you look at life
insurance, there are multiple risks that
come to bear. Uh one is there is
persistency risk from our perspective
and also from the customer's
perspective. What is persistency risk?
Essentially the policy does not continue
till its life. In that instance while
you may think about the fact that it
hurts the company and its financials at
the same time it also hurts the
customer's goals that they were saving
towards. So one obviously has to take
that into account when you look at risk.
The bigger element is around mortality
risk and this is where things start to
step up really.
Uh
most people seem to think that it is not
really a large element but I don't know
if you guys have thought about it one
rupee can buy you 400 rupees of cover
and therefore the kind of leverage that
you have is extremely large.